

Full stack web developer and jack-of-all-trades. Cofounder and CTO of ScoreShots (scoreshots.com). I've spent the last three years taking ScoreShots through to profitability, and I'm currently looking for my next big move. My intent is to leave Fayetteville, and am searching for the right opportunity as close as Raleigh, and as far as the West Coast.

### **Proficiencies**

- React
- Node
- Express
- GraphQL / Apollo
- AWS (Lambda, EC2/ECS, S3, Rekognition, CloudFront, RDS/Aurora, ELB, API Gateway)
- HTML5/CSS3
- yarn, npm
- webpack/babel
- Progressive Web Apps
- jQuery
- HTML Canvas / fabric.js
- Python
- php

# **Projects**

#### Which One Vapes?

Short lived (but insanely popular) web app that used ELO rankings and user voting to compare likelihood of celebrity vaping. Featured on the Daily Dot

## **Education**

2010-2013 | B.S. (INCOMPLETE) **COMPUTER SCIENCE UNC Chapel Hill** 

2008-2010 | MAGNET HIGH SCHOOL North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics

# **Experience**

### 2015 - PRESENT **COFOUNDER & CTO**

#### SCORESHOTS (scoreshots.com)

- Created a React, GraphQL and HTML5 Canvas based social media application for sports teams
- · Maintained several hundred clients, ranging from high school to pro level, including Dallas Mavericks, USGA, and the US Naval Academy
- Manage day-to-day operations of development, design, sales, and customer success teams
- Responsibile for product roadmap, short and long term
- · Designed and developed the vast majority of features, from UI to implementation
- Built MVP, Redesign, and (single-handedly) the revamp that is in use today
- · Wrote business plan and pitched to investors
- · Appeared and gave talks at national collegiate trade shows
- Deeply integrated platform with Stripe, Zendesk, Intercom, and AWS (Lambda, EC2/ECS, ELB, S3, Aurora, Rekognition, CloudFront, API Gateway)
- Developed cloud video rendering flow with realtime preview using HTML5 canvas for previews, and Lamdba/ECS queue for cloud rendering
- Developed another cloud video rendering flow that allowed for realtime preview and customization of After Effects files in browser
- Wrote, implemented and revised protocols for proprietary template flow, customer acquisition and retention, and more
- Wrote and scripted automated customer communication including client check-ups, marketing funnel, and automated demo request flow
- Supervised product rebranding, revamped product marketing website
- · Organized reusable react components, and created an online repository of them for design reference, atomic style
- · Created observability pipeline across all services, tracked bugs across releases
- Used open source libraries, and contributed to said libraries

### 2015 - 2018LEAD DEVELOPER

#### **IMMERSION MEDIA**

- · Created React applications for clients including USA Basketball, the National Wrestling Coaches of America, and the US Soccer for Success Foundation.
- · Managed a development team of 3-4, setting up and executing sprints, setting up development environments and CI/CD pipelines.